Guide to the Records and Papers of Terry Sanford, 1945-1998 UA.03.60.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 1. Duke University. President Terry Sanford Records, 1969-1985.
  - Subseries 1.1. Subject files, 1969-1985, 175 ln. ft. (about 150,000 items
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Contributions (Box 108)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Distribution of report., 8 folders (Box 108)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. General correspondence, 6 folders (Box 108)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Lists (Box 108)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Miscellaneous, 7 folders (Box 108)
    - President's Dining Room, 1982 (Box 109)
    - President's House, [1979-1983] (Box 109)
    - President's Office. Congressional Correspondence, 1970-1984, 6 folders (Box 109)
    - President's Office. Memos for the record (Box 109)
    - President's Office. Office automation, VTR-II, etc. (Box 109)
    - President's Office. Personnel (RESTRICTED) (Box 109)
      (RESTRICTED)
    - President's Office. Plan of Operation (Box 109)
    - President's Office. President's Schedule, 1970-1974 (Box 109)
    - President's Office. Sanford, Terry. Sabbatical (Box 109)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Negative replies to requests for grants) (Box 109)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Panel (Box 109)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Report [A Statement of Purpose for Political Parties] (Box 109)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Reports, requests for Presidential Nominations Forum. Sessions 1-4, 4 folders (Box 109)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. Toronto, May-June, 1981 (Box 109)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum. [The Presidential Selection Process, A Conference Sponsored by The American Bar Association and The Johnson Foundation, 1981] (Box 109)
    - Presidential Primaries Conference, April 24-26, 1985, Ann Arbor, Michigan (Box 109)
    - Presidential Primaries. Projects for Media Coverage (Box 109)
    - Presidents' Institute. Cornell University, June 21-26, 1970 (Box 109)
    - President's Office. Sanford, Terry. Diary, 1970-1971 (Box 110)
    - President's Office. Smyer, Mick, 1976 [Research Assistant] (Box 110)
    - President's Office. Source Data Book [ 1969. Briefing book] (Box 110)
    - President's Office. Student lunches, 1972 (Box 110)
    - President's Office. Transportation and vehicle records (Box 110)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 110)
    - Price, James L., 1970-1978 [Vice-Provost and Dean of Undergradaute Education] (Box 110)
    - Primate Facility (Box 110)
    - Provost's Summary of Information to President Sanford, 1-1-70. (Box 110)
    - Provost, 1970-1971. John O. Blackburn (Box 110)
    - Provost, 1970. Marcus E. Hobbs (Box 110)
    - Provost, 1971-1978. Frederic N. Cleaveland (Box 110)
    - Provost, 1978-1982. William Bevan (Box 110)
    - Provost, 1983-1985. Phillip Griffiths (Box 110)
    - Psychiatric Institute Foundation, 1976 [Sex Roles Conference] (Box 110)
    - Publications Office, 1969, 1977-1981 (Box 110)
    - Pye, A. Kenneth, 1971-1974 [University Counsel], 4 folders (Box 110)
    - Pye, A. Kenneth, 1973-1976 [Dean, Law School] (Box 110)
    - Q. General correspondence (Box 111)
    - Questionnaires, 1978-1985, 6 folders (Box 111)
    - Questionnaires, Barnard College, 1979 (Box 111)
    - R. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 12 folders (Box 111)
    - Racquetball, [1977-1983] (Box 111)
    - Radio Shack, Tandy Corp. (Box 111)
    - Radio. WDBS, 1967-1985, 3 folders (Box 111)
    - Rankin, Mrs. Robert (Box 111)
    - Readers' Digest, 1974 [DeWitt Wallace] (Box 111)
    - Reading Programs, 1977-1983. Anne H. Adams (Box 111)
    - Reagan, Ronald. President (Box 111)
    - Real Estate, 1979-1985, 8 folders (Box 112)
    - Real Estate. Riverbend [Wake County, NC] (Box 112)
    - Real Estate. White Oaks [Duke Home, Charlotte, NC] (Box 112)
    - Recommendations, 1974-1980, 11 folders (Box 112)
      NOTE:Recommendations and reference files are RESTRICTED
    - Recommendations, 1981-1985, 8 folders (Box 113)
    - Recommendations, Students. (Box 113)
    - Recycling and sales (Box 113)
    - Reference requests, 1970-1980, 9 folders (Box 113)
    - Reference requests, 1981-1985, 8 folders (Box 114)
    - Referral Logs -are filed separately (Box 114)
    - Regan, Don, 1971 (Box 114)
    - Regional Programs, Office of. 1967-1970. [Hopkins, Everett. Colver, Robert] (Box 114)
    - Registrar's Office, 1970-1984 (Box 114)
    - Reich, Alan A. [1982-1983] (Box 114)
    - Religious Groups Space, 1973 (Box 114)
    - Research Support, Office of, 1980-1984 (Box 114)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1970-1985, 5 folders (Box 114)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1970-1980, 18 folders (Box 115)
    - Research Triangle Institute&Research Triangle Foundation Appointments, [1967-1983] (Box 116)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1981-1985, 5 folders (Box 116)
    - Research Triangle International Visitors Center, 1973-1977 (Box 116)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1970-1981 [general] (Box 116)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps, Air Force, 1970-1983 (Box 116)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps, Army, 1983- (Box 116)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps, Navy, 1970-1985 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. Clippings, 1980 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. East Campus, 1980-1981 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. Education Dept., 1980-1982 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. General correspondence and reports, 1980-1981 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. Health, Physical Education, and Recreation Dept., 1980-1981 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. News releases, 1980 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. Nursing Education Planning Task Force, 1980-1982 (Box 116)
    - Retrenchment. Nursing School, 1980-1981 (Box 116)
    - Rhine, J.B., [1977-1979] (Box 117)
    - Rhodes Scholars, 1970-1984 (Box 117)
    - Ross, J. David, 1 979-1981 (Box 117)
    - Rotary [Club of Durham], 1970-1981 (Box 117)
    - S. General correspondence, 1970-1982, 13 folders (Box 117)
    - S. General correspondence, 1983-1985, 3 folders (Box 118)
    - SALT, 1979 [Strategic Arms Limitations Talks] (Box 118)
    - Saint Andrews Presbyterian College, Laurinburg, NC. 1971- 1984 (Box 118)
    - Saturday Review [magazine], 1979-1981 (Box 118)
    - Saudi Arabia, 1979-1981 (Box 118)
    - Sawyer, Robert N., 1976-1982 (Box 118)
    - School situation, 1973-1978 [relates to poor conditions in Durham public schools, and proposals to alleviate them, including a school run by the University], 3 folders (Box 118)
    - Sea Grant Studies, [1966-1970] [grants for oceanographc research] (Box 118)
    - Security Office, 1970-1985 (Box 118)
    - Semans, Mary and Jim (Box 118)
    - Shroud of Turin, [ 1982-1984. Alan D. Whanger] (Box 118)
    - Skarulis, Patricia C., Vice Chancellor for Information Systems, [1983-1985] (Box 118)
    - Sloan Colloquium on Communications and Telecommunications Policy, 1984-1985 (Box 118)
    - Smithsonian Project, [1982] (Box 118)
    - Society for Religion in Higher Education, 1975 (Box 118)
    - Solie, Guy, 1972- [Special Assistant to the President] (Box 118)
    - South Africa, 1977-1985, 3 folders (Box 118)
    - South Africa. Divestment. Social Implications of Duke Investment Policy. (Box 118)
    - South Africa. International Telephone and Telegraph (Box 118)
    - South Africa. Universities' policies (Box 118)
    - South Asia Studies in the Carolinas-Virgina Region, [Association ...], 1971 (Box 119)
    - Southeast Consortium for International Development, [1977] (Box 119)
    - Southeastern Council of Foundations, 1973-1974 (Box 119)
    - Southeastern Institute of Medieval and Renaissance Studies, [1974-1979] (Box 119)
    - Southeastern Regional Association of Physical Plant Administrators of Universities and Colleges, 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Southeastern Regional Education Laboratory, [1985] (Box 119)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, Inc., 1970-1985 (Box 119)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, Inc. (Box 119)
    - Duke University's Fifth Year Essay Report, 1971 (Box 119)
    - Southern Atlantic States Association for Asian and AfricanStudies, [1981-1982] (Box 119)
    - Southern Educational Communications Association, [1970] (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1976-1985 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Address lists, 1971 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Babcock Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Beyle, Thad, 1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Business, Materials, etc., 1971-1972 [financial records] (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Employment Applications, 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Ford Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Foundation correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Governors' correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Imprest cash forms, etc., 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Invoices, 1972 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 [includes descriptive brochure, briefing book, minutes, and miscellanous correspondence] (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. News clippings, 1971 (Box 119)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Others' correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 120)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board. Smith Richardson Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 120)
    - Southern Regional Education Board, 1970-1984 (Box 120)
    - Southern University Conference, 1974-1981 (Box 120)
    - Southern Water Resource and Pollution Control Conference, 1970. E.H. Bryan (Box 120)
    - Spaulding, Asa T., 1971-1980 (Box 120)
    - Special Events, 1971-1984. Paul Vick. Janet Sanfilippo (Box 120)
    - Statue of Liberty [Centennial Celebration, 1983-1984] (Box 120)
    - Student awards, [1981-1985] (Box 120)
    - Student cases, 1970-1985 (8f). [RESTRICTED] (Box 120)
      [RESTRICTED]
    - Student government associations (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Angier B. Duke Scholarship, 1970-1971. Bill Garrison and Tom Drew (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Community Internship Program, [Syracuse University], 1972 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Drug study, 1970-1971. Tom Drew (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Duke-Durham Community Relationships, 1971 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Durham Research Associates, 1970. Bill Garrison (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Environmental study, 1970-1971. Bill Garrison (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Freshman dinners, 1971 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Hospital sessions, 1972 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. International programs - S.C. (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Journalism, 1972. Bill Garrison (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Library question, 1971. [The Branson Committee Report] (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Miscellaneous material, 1970-1972 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Museum Intern Program, 1971-1972. Mary Woods. (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Museum of African Art Exhibit, 1971. Mary Woods (Box 120)
    - Student interns. North Carolina. State Internship Program, 1971 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Original sessions, 1971. [Possible projects] (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Peace and Conflict Resolution, 1971 (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Program in the Arts, 1971-1972. Mary (Box 120)
    - Woods, Bill Garrison, Curt Moffatt. (Box 120)
    - Student interns. Program in the Arts, 1971-1972. Mary Woods, Bill Garrison, Curt Moffatt., 8 folders (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Public School Creative Arts Proposal, 1972 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Publications, 1971. (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Religious organizations (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Revenue sharing, 1971 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Safety report, 1970-1972. (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Sanford for President, 1972. [Students for Sanford] (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Scotland estate, 1971 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Southern Regional Growth Board, 1971 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Student abortion loan program, 1971 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Student internship programs, 1972 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Students for summer staff, 1971 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Study Abroad, 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Student interns. University planning, 1971-1972 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Women studies, 1971 (Box 121)
    - Student interns. Year in Action program, 1971. Tom Drew, 4 folders (Box 121)
    - Student Petitions, Post Office, n.d. (Box 122)
    - Student petitions, 1970-1979 (Box 122)
    - Student petitions, ITT, 1976-1977. Radical Academics Union (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1968-1970 (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May. Clippings (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May. Letters answered (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May. Letters answered [samples for the Board of Trustees] (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May. Letters unanswered (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May. Replies [to Sanford's letter] (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970 May. Telegrams (Box 122)
    - Student unrest, 1970. Printed matter (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. Allen Building Takeover, 1969, 3 folders (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. Allen Building Takeover, 1969. Scrapbook [Includes interview transcripts] (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. March for Peace, April 24, 1971 (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. Report of the President's Commission on Campus Unrest, 1970 (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. Spiro Agnew, 1970 (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. University Policy Toward Dissent, 1971 (Box 122)
    - Student unrest. University of California, 1966- (Box 122)
    - Students. ASDU. Abortion Committee, 1971 (Box 123)
      NOTE:Some Students files may be RESTRICTED
    - Students. ASDU. Athletic Facility and Program Survey, 1982 (Box 123)
    - Students. ASDU. Report on Tuition, 1984 (Box 123)
    - Students. ASDU. Special [report on ASDU's role], 1975-1976. Students. ASDU. Task Force on Black / White Relations, 1982 (Box 123)
    - Students. Alpha Epsilon Pi Fraternity, 1984 (Box 123)
    - Students. American Student Federation, 1979 (Box 123)
    - Students. Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1970-1985, 5 folders (Box 123)
    - Students. Association of African Students, 1971-1976 (Box 123)
    - Students. Beta Phi Zeta, 1982 (Box 123)
    - Students. Conference on Career Choices, 1982 (Box 123)
    - Students. Deaths, [1965-1985] (Box 123)
    - Students. Duke Investment Club, [1984] (Box 123)
    - Students. Fraternities and Sororities, 1970-1985 (Box 123)
    - Students. Freshman Orientation, [1976-1985] (Box 123)
    - Students. Gay Alliance, 1974 (Box 123)
    - Students. Graduate Student Association, [1971-1975] (Box 123)
    - Students. Graduate and Professional Student Council, [1984-1985] (Box 123)
    - Students. Housing (Box 123)
    - Students. Interview with a group of seniors, April 22, 1974 [Transcript] (Box 123)
    - Students. Judicial Board (Box 123)
    - Students. Law Students Against the War, Inc., [1970] (Box 123)
    - Students. Letters from parents, 1971-1977, 7 folders (Box 123)
    - Students. Letters from parents, 1978-1985, 9 folders (Box 124)
    - Students. Loans (Alumni) (Box 124)
    - Students. Miscellaneous, 1970-1985, 15 folders (Box 124)
    - Students. Movement for Shared Authority, 1975 (Box 125)
    - Students. Pitchforks, 1980-1982 (Box 125)
    - Students. Political Activity (Box 125)
    - Students. Political Science (Box 125)
    - Students. Publications (Box 125)
    - Students. Residential Life (Box 125)
    - Students. Scholarships, [1979-1985] (Box 125)
    - Students. Suppers (Box 125)
    - Students. Symposium: Peacekeeping in a Nuclear Age, [1984] (Box 125)
    - Students. YMCA / YWCA (Box 125)
    - Students. Yearbook [Chanticleer], 1970-1985 (Box 125)
    - Sudler, Louis J., Prize in the Arts, 1983 (Box 125)
    - Summer Internships, 1971-1985 (Box 125)
    - Summer Session, 1970-1976 (Box 125)
    - Summer Session, 1974-1983 (Box 125)
    - Summer Session. Pre-College Program, 1978-1979 (Box 125)
    - Summer Transitional Program, 1971, 1983-1985 (Box 125)
    - Superannuates, 1970-1973, 4 folders (Box 125)
    - Superannuates. Pattern Letters, [1951-1973] (Box 125)
    - Telephone logs, 11/30/1970 - 1/30/1973 (Box 125)
    - Telephone logs, 1973-1985 (Box 126)
    - T. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 9 folders (Box 127)
    - Talent Identification Program, 1980-1985, 6 folders (Box 127)
    - Tarr, Curtis, 1980-1981 (Box 127)
    - Tax bills (HR 14844) [Correspondence with NC legislators] (Box 127)
    - Tax credit, tuition, 1977-1978 (Box 127)
    - Tax reform. Senate hearing, 4/8/76 [testimony] (Box 127)
    - Tax. IRS, N.C. Dept. of Revenue, etc. [1970-1975] (Box 127)
    - Taxes, 1979-1982 (Box 127)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, [1972-1979] (Box 127)
    - Telephone messages, 1981-1985, 5 folders (Box 127)
    - Telephone service, 1972-1981 (Box 127)
    - Thatcher, Margaret, 1982-1983 (Box 128)
    - Title IX [nine], 1979-1984, 4 folders (Box 128)
    - Triangle Center for Voluntary Action, Inc. (TCVA), 1971-1972 (Box 128)
    - Triangle J Council of Governments, 1972 (Box 128)
    - Triangle J Council of Governments, 1979-1984, 3 folders (Box 128)
    - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, Inc. (TUCASI), 1976-1985 (Box 128)
    - Triangle Universities Computation Center, 1965-1983 (Box 128)
    - Triangle Universities Consortium on Air Pollution, 1969-1974 (Box 128)
    - Triangle Universities Nuclear Laboratory, 1972 (Box 128)
    - Triangle World Affairs Center, 1978-1979 (Box 128)
    - Trinity College Teaching Consultant. Pelham Wilder, 1983 (Box 128)
    - Trinity College of Arts and Sciences. Restructuring Undergraduate Education, 1967-1972 (Box 128)
    - Trustees, Board of. [TS personal file?] (Box 128)
      NOTE:Trustee files are RESTRICTED
    - Trustees. Agenda [items], 1980-1984 (Box 128)
    - Trustees. Appointments, [1970-1984] [correspondence, terms, election results, lists, etc.] (Box 128)
    - Trustees. Bylaws [of the University, 1970] (Confidential) (Box 128)
    - Trustees. Dinners for (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Executive Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Executive Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Executive Committee. Chancellor Pye's Report on the Financing of Intercollegiate Athletics. [1973?] (Box 129)
    - Trustees. General correspondence, 1970-1983, 4 folders (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Knight, Douglas M., last days at Duke, 1966-1969 (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Manual for (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Marshall, Roger. Secretary (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Nominations, 1982-1985, 4 folders (Box 129)
    - Trustees. Powell, Rufus, Secretary (Box 129)
    - Trustees. President's Mailings to (Box 129)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1968-1972 (Box 129)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1970 (Box 129)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1972 (Box 129)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1975 (Box 130)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1977 (Box 130)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1981 (Box 130)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1984 (Box 130)
    - Trustees. President's Report to, 1985 (Box 130)
    - Trustees, Student / young, selection of (Box 130)
    - Trustees. Report of the Special Committee on the Functions and Organization of the Board of Trustees, December, 1969 (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Baugh, P.J. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Bays, Carl (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Benenson, Edward H. [see also Benenson - Awards] (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Boulware, C.E. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Brian, Blanche, (Mrs. Earl W.) (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Brown, Werner C. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Cannon, William R., 1970-1972 (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Caudle, Lloyd C. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Cook, Samuel DuBois (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Cooper, Alyse Smith (Mrs. Wilbur N.) (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Craven, James Braxton, Jr., Judge (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Cuninggim, Merrimon (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Dale, Kathleen and Francis (Frank) (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Davis, Walter[see also Davis, and G & G] (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Deane, Disque D. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: deButts, John (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Dole, Elizabeth Hanford (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Donnell, Edward S. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Drill, Isobel Craven (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Duke, Anthony Drexel (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Edgerton, N. Edward (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Espy, Sally Kleberg (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Faircloth, Nancy Bryan (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Finch, Thomas A., 1971-1983 (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Forlines, John A., Jr. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Fuqua, J.B. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Garrett, Nathan F. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Goodson, W. Kenneth (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hanes, P. Huber, Jr., 1954-1973 (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hanks, Nancy (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hardesty, C. Howard, Jr. (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hardin, Paul, 1970-1974 (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Harris, Margaret (Mrs. R. Kennedy) (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Harriss, J. Welch (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hart, Milledge (Mitch) (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hillman, Jennifer (Box 130)
    - Trustees: Hoadley, Walter E., 1970-1973 (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Holloway, Benjamin D. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Horne, Josh (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Houck, C.B. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Hudson, Fitzgerald S. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Hunt, Alfred M. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Ives, Page H. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Ivey, George M. and Ivey, Groves (Mrs. George M.) (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Jones, Edwin L., 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Kearns, Amos (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Keesee, Thomas (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Kirby, Wallace H. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Knowles, John H., M.D. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Kurzweil, Jeff (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Lane, William A., Jr. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Lumiansky, Robert M. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Maisel, David R. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: McGhee, George C. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: McMahon, John Alexander [Chairman], 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Miller, Ben N. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Moore, John Kevin (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Muller, William H., Jr., M.D. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Murphy, Charles S. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Nasher, Raymond D. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Nease, Edgar H. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Osteen, E. Powell, Jr. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Perkins, Thomas L. [Duke Endowment] (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Perry, Clifford W. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Pickens, Marshall I. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Pinnix, Robert H. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Pratt, Edmund T. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Rausch, Henry E. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Reid, Elizabeth Brooks (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Rhyne, Charles S. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Robinson, Frederick (Rick) (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Schaefer, Norb F. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Semans, Mary Duke Biddle Trent (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Sherrill, Frank O. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Simpson, Dorothy L. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Smith, J. Raymond (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Sorley, Kathleen (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Southgate, Thomas F., Jr. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Stern, Kay Goodman, Mrs. Sidney J. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Stockton, Thomas B. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Tannenbaum, Jack and Lea (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Temple, Arthur (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Thigpen, Richard E., Sr. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Tift, Susan E. (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Tisdale, Wright (Box 131)
    - Trustees: Towe, Kenneth C. (Box 132)
    - Trustees: Upchurch, Walter M., Jr. (Box 132)
    - Trustees: Von Canon, Fred (Box 132)
    - Trustees: Wade, Charles B., 1966-1985, 4 folders (Box 132)
    - Trustees: Wallace, George R. (Box 132)